allie goodson

Designer & Artist

Portfolio

https://allie.goodson.dev

Contact

allie@goodson.dev 510.493.6531

Experience Highlights

UX/UI Design

Google UX Design Course — June 2021 – Present Currently enrolled in a design course to develop skills in generative research, design principles, prototyping, and design thinking. **Key Projects:**

Visual Designer, UX/UI Designer

Clean SF — allie.goodson.dev/cleansf

- > Rapidly ideated and validated designs through sketches, prototypes, and user testing to produce a high-fidelity prototype from MVP's
- > Presented documentation, site map, annotated wireframes, and interactive prototypes
- > Created a style guide, color palette, typography, new logo, and UI components

Visual Designer, UX/UI Designer

business and user goals

Marshawarma — allie.goodson.dev/marshawarma

 Conceptualized and produced an eCommerce app using design thinking
Conducted user research and competitive analysis to ensure alignment between

Education

Google UX Design Course June 2021 – Present

San Jose State University

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Digital Media Art December 2014 — San Jose, CA

Skills

Rapid Prototyping Interactive Prototyping Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, Lightroom, Sketchup

Professional Experience

Receptionist — Kaiser Permanente

San Jose, CA | June 2015 - August 2021

- > Continuously handle inbound calls
- > Work collaboratively with physicians, medical assistants and other care team members
- >Maintain compliance with HIPAA

Wellness Coach — YMCA

San Jose, CA | May 2014 – June 2015

- > Monitor the wellness center as members use the equipment to ensure their general safety and equipment function
- > Demonstrate correct form and technique during wellness consultations and healthy lifestyles sessions
- > Promote and sell personal training and additional YMCA health & wellness services & programs

Events

Parking Day

Group Show, Fall 2013 First Street — San Jose, CA

Olallieberry

Individual Show, November 17-21, 2014 Herbert Sanders Gallery — San Jose, CA